Thank you for watching!
Thanks for your work!
I'll be back soon with a new episode of "Halo! This time we have with us Ayumi Ishida from Morning Musume。 24 and Wakana Matsumoto from Angeleum!
And Wakana Matsumoto from Angulum.
This time, we'll be joined by these two, so please stay with us until the end.
Thank you very much.
Today, March 13th, is Sandwich Day.
Sandwich Day.
I heard there's such a thing.
Wakana, you make bread at home, too.
Yes, on anniversaries, like Halloween and Christmas.
I sometimes make bread on those days.
I also make sweets to pass the time or to refresh myself.
Recently, there's carrot cake, right?
By the way, carrot cake
I like it.
It makes me happy.
Carrot cake.
The kind with cinnamon.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, carrot cake, it's got carrots in it and cinnamon and spices.
I haven't had too many people around me say they like it.
So I guess it's not to everyone's taste.
I'm glad you like it.
I'm glad.
That carrot cake...
I found a recipe for a scone version of carrot cake and I made it recently.
I tried it recently and it was delicious.
But I wasn't sure if it would taste good when other people ate it.
I'm not sure.
Well, it certainly has a unique taste, doesn't it?
I'd love to try it!
I should have brought it today.
I wish I could have had it.
Thank you, but I'm not so sure.
Morning Musume。24コンサートツアー春
More Morning Musume。 is about to start!
will start on March 16th, the first day of the tour.
March 16th, which means that the first day of the tour will be Rio Kitagawa's birthday!
Oh!
I'm sure everyone is looking forward to it.
I'm sure they are expecting it to be a lot of fun.
Of course, I'll do my best to make it happen.
I'll do my best after rehearsals.
Now that you have a new organization...
Yes, yes, yes!
I really want to go see the show!
Please come and see the final performance.
Yes...
Angelem is...
Angulum concert tour 2024 Spring Secret Secret will start on the 1st.
This tour is for Rikako Sasaki's graduation tour.
Yes.
It's the last tour.
It's her hometown concert.
Yes.
We'll be performing in Kesennuma City.
I'm happy too!
We'll be performing in Kawamura-san's hometown in Kochi Prefecture.
We often perform in the members' hometowns.
I hope we can make many more memories together as the 11 of us.
As for the title "Secret Secret"...
Are you still satisfied with the concept?
I was told that if you do Secret twice in a row, it turns into Kyokoku.
So I hope we can show you the culmination of the 11 of us.
I hope we can all do our best to show the culmination of the 11 of us.
I see.
It's like opening one more drawer for everyone.
I guess that's what it means.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll do my best.
Now, please take a look at this video.
Here you go.
Now, I'd like to introduce our new trainees who joined us last month.
Now, let's have a look at our new trainees.
I'm Hana Shimokawa, a junior high school student from Kanagawa prefecture.
I'm from Kanagawa prefecture, so I love Ikei-kei Ramen and Strawberry Daifuku!
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you for your hard work!
I'm Yurika Asano, an eighth grader from Kanagawa prefecture.
My favorite food is kimuchi nabe, chicken wings and ramen!
I look forward to working with you!
I'm Chihiro Miyakoshi, a 13-year-old first-year junior high school student from Tokyo. My favorite food is curry rice, hamburger and sushi rice. I am looking forward to working with you.
I am Itsuki Nishimura, a first-year junior high school student from Kanagawa Prefecture. My favorite food is salmon and grilled salmon roe. I am looking forward to working with you.
I am Yume Soma, a first-year junior high school student from Saitama. My favorite food is hamburgers and sweets in general. I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
I am Mano Ohtsubo, a sixth grader from Kanagawa Prefecture.
My favorite food is omu-rice, takoyaki and hitsu-mabushi. I look forward to working with you.
I am Hikari Yoshida, a 6th grader from Tokyo. My favorite food is yakiniku and salmon roe made by my mom. I look forward to working with you.
I am Meisa Sugihara, a 6th grader from Hyogo. My favorite food is all kinds of fruit, fruit candy, and udon noodles made by my mom. I am looking forward to working with you.
My name is Roha Hattori, a 5th grader from Aichi Prefecture. My favorite food is stewed hamburger steak made by my mom and pumpkin curry made by my dad. Please take care of me.
Yes, thank you all very much.
Next, I'd like to introduce our new trainees, the nine of you who just met with us.
Please come in!
Please join us!
Please subscribe to our channel!
I may look like an honor student, but I'm just a regular actress.
Girls who want to stand out.
I want to be prettier.
Flutter, flutter, flutter.
Three days, three days, three days.
Sunset, sunset, daytime, daytime.
I can't go any higher.
Hang in there. That's me right now.
I want to fall in love with a girl
It's a little early for that, don't you think?
I'll give myself a little more gakko
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah Kyoukoukyou-chan
This is what happens when I express my riding mood
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, look at me.
Don't laugh.
Home!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah Ultra-jump
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Ultra-jump.
I'm gonna shock it out of my head.
That's what happens when you shock your head.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Ultra-jumping.
It doesn't matter if you're like me
Even if you fall in love with me
Recovered.
Yes, I'm in love with you.
Natsuyasihara
Clara
depende
aspect
orship
вместе
Clay
Enjoying it? Watch the rest of the video!
This is Haroste, featuring Ayumi Ishida of Morning Musume 24 and Wakana Matsumoto of Angelem.
and Wakana Matsumoto of Angeleum.
We'd like to talk a little bit about each other from here.
First, I will ask you a few questions.
So let's answer in a quick tempo without thinking too much.
Yes, I'll do my best to keep up the tempo.
Tell me about the recent news events.
I went out with Tsutsuki Rokochan of Ochanoma.
Tomorrow is White Day, the day when Smileage's "Becoming an adult" was released.
Wakana, when do you think it is difficult to be an adult?
I get sleepy at night.
She's so cute!
Is there anything you are working on for the spring tour?
Yes, I'm working on my physical strength.
What do you think of Mei Yamazaki?
Well, she talks very calmly.
I think she is very decisive and decides on the menu very quickly.
I see.
That's interesting.
Three years have passed since you joined Angstrom.
What kind of person do you think you've become during this time?
I think I've gained the ability to see what's going on around me.
Yes, I have.
Thank you very much.
I just, um...
I just wanted to ask you a cute question.
And you already have.
Mei Yamazaki really likes you, Wakana.
It fits so well. I can feel it.
I can feel it.
That's...
Yes.
Even when you're not around.
"I went out with Wakana the other day.
"Wakana did this and that for me.
I hear that a lot.
I see.
That's right.
He really likes her.
And the other day, when we were talking. I told him that I'm going to shoot with Wakana-chan.
She said, "Oh, that's nice.
I see.
I'm going to ask you a question or two.
I said I'll ask about Mei.
Yes, I will.
I'm glad you asked.
Are you watching, Mr. Yamazaki?
Hey...
Thank you very much
That was a cute answer.
Yes.
Decisiveness I can see.
It was pretty much like, "Mei, I'm going to go with this one.
That's true.
You decide really fast.
I thought that was interesting.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
And you know what?
Yes, sir.
You don't sleep at night?
Oh, yes.
I usually go to bed early and get up early.
Yes.
I use the time to weigh my body weight.
I get very sleepy around 11:00 p.m.
Yes, yes, yes.
And at around 12 o'clock, I turn off the power.
It turns off and goes "ding ding".
Yes, yes.
Adults tend to work hard at night, don't they?
It's true that some people have to work until nighttime.
That kind of thing is a little too much for some of them.
Ha-ha-ha.
In that case, there are those who can be active in the morning, and it's better not to break that rhythm.
I think it's good to be an adult like that, and I'm going to do my best.
Thank you very much.
I'll try to do my best.
me
ni
ni ni
Haloste
Next, I would like to ask Mr. Ishida a question from me.
Please do.
What are you secretly looking forward to this spring?
I want to go strawberry picking.
Your tour starts this weekend.
Do you have a routine right before a live performance?
Yes, I give high-fives to the members and staff.
Season 11 of Halo Pro Dance Academy will start in about a month, on April 18.
What are the highlights of the new season?
We have invited Tsukushi-san as a teacher this time.
Of course, Tsukushi-san's dance will be the highlight of this season.
We also had a moment when each of us had a free dance.
It was nerve-wracking, but we did our best.
And as we were doing the free dance, Mr. Kaya, the MC, and the two dancers were talking about how they were going to do it.
Kaya-san, the two MCs, also danced, so please pay attention to them.
I want to see it!
Which Angelem member would you like to sing with?
Yes, Ayana Kawamura.
She has been a member of Morning Musume。
It's been three and a half months since the group took its current form.
What is the best word to describe the current 13 members?
True.
Oh, that was a little too true at the end.
Thank you very much.
Okay, the question I wanted to ask is.
Which member of Angelem would you like to sing with?
Ms. Kawamura.
I personally really like Ayana Kawamura's voice.
There's a kindness in it, but there's also a sincerity.
Yeah, yeah.
And during the live performance...
Her concentration...
Yes.
I admire her attitude towards the live performance, so I always look up to her when I see her perform, so I sang with her and I sang with her.
I mean, I'd rather follow her.
I'd like to bask in the sound of her voice from back then.
Your voice really makes me feel comfortable when I'm on stage with you.
It's so comfortable to be on stage with you.
But you're also both cool and cute.
I really love your voice.
And one more thing.
I think one more thing that's perfect for Morning Musume。 I think it's perfect for Morning Musume。
New! New new new!
New new new!
Yes, new, new, new!
I think it's definitely new again.
After Mizuki Fukumura's graduation
I think the parts she sang are very impressive.
So it's refreshing to see her singing those memorable parts.
So it's refreshing to see her singing those memorable parts even though we're in the same group.
I thought it was cool.
I think it's cool that she's going to express herself in a new way.
I think that's what I want people to see in the future Morning Musume。 I think that's what I want people to see in the future of Morning Musume。
Yes.
Yes, ma'am.
So for the next spring tour...
I hope you'll pay attention to the song divisions.
I hope you enjoy it.
Hello! We'll be right back with more after this.
Thank you for watching!
I'm Kimiyami Natsuyaki. I am Hana Goto of Angelem. Please give me your regards.
I will do my best. What are you going to make this time? Today I'm going to make a meat pie.
I've never eaten one before. You've never had a meat pie? I see. I have.
But you don't have a chance to eat it. You can't even find it in stores.
I'm looking forward to it. How should I do it?
Isn't it a little dry? Right now. It's like this, but it's just a little bit more. It's all right now.
Now, where would you like to start this time? Yes, I'm going to start with the pie. Now it's time to finish the pie,
We are going to coat the surface of the pie with egg yolk. We'll use the eggshell to go back and forth, back and forth, so it doesn't crack.
I've got yellow in it. Help! This way, this way, this way.
Double it.
Here. Is it OK because I'm mixing it after all? It would be better if we put a little water in it, but it will dry out again, so let's leave it as it is.
Okay, I'll leave it as it is. I got it.
It is soft. Yes, it's already soft, so it's better to rub it lightly.
Oh. And if you leave it like this, it's too thick, so I want to stretch it a little. This way. This way. Yes, yes, yes. Oh.
Oh, it looks good. Then, if you do it this way, too, it's good. 1, 2, 3.
One, two, three. Okay, well, let's just go with this one. Yes.
Okay, let's make this one a little flat to put it on. Wow, cute. Flatten it. Make it flat.
If you make it flat, it's just right. That's good. Yes, it's good. How about it? A little more. A little more.
A little more. Bench press. Yes, yes, yes. More, more, more. More presses. More. Yes . Yes. Then you can put it in the middle.
Oh. Wow. Cute. Overall. Suddenly foreign. No, like a foreign child.
But it's nice. Yes, it's good. Cut like this, and cut this one in the same way, please. First, cut.
Yes. Use the tip. Yes, yes, yes. Use the tip. Okay, like this, and then stack them on top of each other like this. Wow, it looks like a fish.
Yes. Yes.
Yes. Yes, indeed. Yes. Then, please open it.
Open? I'm going to open the gap on purpose.
Why? Yes. Here. Here is the miyamizu point. Yes.
You don't need to make air holes. It's okay. It's okay.
What? What do you mean? There is a type of pie that is completely encased.
Pies are usually wrapped like this. Yes. Then, the inside of the pie is, how shall I say it, too high. I mean, the inside of the pie rises too high.
Really? And in this case, the hole is already open. Yes, it's okay.
So, it's okay. Okay.
Now, I added a little water, and you can mix it with your fingers.
Oh, wow. It's like seaweed, isn't it? It's amazing. Yes, it is.
Pat-pat-pat-pat. It's a little like making pastries. Yes, it is. Yes, it is. Same here.
Patapapapata. This one goes like this, too.
If it's too hard, it might be hard to light. Worship this.
Do it like this. Then, fold it a little bit and crush it. I crush it. Yes, it's done. It's done.
Oh, it looks like bread. Yes, it looks like bread. It sure looks like bread.
And then you cut the whole thing into little decorative slices.
Even though I cut a lot of it, by raising it, it doesn't really show.
I don't know.
Well, I'm going to cut a lot now.
Yes.
Yes. I did it. It's done.
Yes. And now, let's clean up the whole area again. You can paint it all over again.
Boldly?
Yes.
Isn't that good? Always.
Down here, on this cookie sheet.
Soot, soot, soot.
Yes, yes.
Okay.
Three, two, one.
Bring it in, doctor.
There is a slight discrepancy, isn't there?
There is a slight discrepancy.
When I was doing the eggs like this, I was already putting the eggs in when I was ready to put them in, and so on.
You are not in sync with each other?
Our paces are not in sync.
Not meshing? You mean, like, "Yes," right, Sensei?
Three, two, one, you're a little slow.
What are you doing?
We're a little off.
That's funny.
It's not working.
But you're getting better at it, so...
Yeah, it's... You're getting better. I'm sure of it.
I did it. Pro-professional.
Become a pro-professional.
Yeah.
I'm done with this.
All I have to do now is bake it.
It's done.
Then, please put it in.
I'm counting on you.
Ta-da.
Ta-da!
How many steps?
It's hot, right here.
Start in the middle.
From the middle.
Ta-da.
Ta-da!
Oh, yeah.
Now what shall we do next?
Well, I'd like to make a sauce...
Yes!
A lot. A little bit.
Maybe we should start a fire.
Ignite it!
Yes, sir.
Medium fire? Medium?
Let's just wait for medium heat.
If it comes to a boil...
Oh, here it comes.
This has alcohol in it, so it will catch fire.
Tilt it to the side.
Oh!
Maybe a little less.
Is this supposed to be temperate?
It's got a concentrated sweetness to it.
Sauce?
It's a sauce.
How did this get here?
It's a little thick.
Oh, my God! Because it's...
It's got a lot of sugar.
It drains the water out.
Oh, yeah, it smells sweet.
Ketchup and sauce, about 40 each.
About three tablespoons.
Three tablespoons. That's a lot.
Now mix it all together.
Stir, stir, stir.
Bring it to a boil for a minute.
Yes, I can use it for pie today
Both of them
You can use it for hamburgers, too.
So I learned how to make hamburger sauce.
That's right.
Now get out a spoon.
Taste it.
Yes!
If it's okay.
Not too hot?
Hey!
It smells so good, I'd like to serve it.
Wow! I'm so excited!
It's a little hot. Not at all.
Good job!
Wow! That's a lot of gravy.
It's really juicy!
And, generally speaking, it's OK as long as there are juices coming out of the meat.
But the burn marks...
I use a metal skewer.
I'll check the temperature.
Okay, then, I'll ask them to bathe in hot water.
Here, in the middle, give it a quick zap.
Yes!
One push with the gun.
Oh, it's done!
Ready, go!
Oh!
That's good. That's good.
Oh, my God! It's baked!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's good.
Take this and put it all over here.
Put a lot of it on top and spread it out a little bit.
Can I spread it out more?
Can I spread it out more? It's pretty big.
You can't even see the sauce.
That's right. It's hidden.
Not if you can't see it.
Maybe you should have your cross section facing left.
Left? That way?
That way. Yes, yes, yes.
That's good.
I think it's just right.
Yes, sir.
Neat pie. It's done.
The meat pie is ready.
Yay! It's done.
How do you like it?
It's so beautifully done.
Really beautifully done.
I think I did a good job with the egg depression and broth, so the pie turned out shiny and pretty.
It is wonderful.
Please try it right away.
Yes, I will. Bon appétit.
We've had it.
It turned out really delicious.
You said you have never cooked much,
How was it cooking?
It was a lot of fun,
I enjoyed cooking from scratch like this,
I became very attached to the food I made from scratch and ate the finished product myself.
Was it good?
It was delicious.
The sauce tasted great, too,
I thought it was a great combination.
It was great.
How did you like it, sir? How was it cooking together?
It was very fast-paced,
It was hard to keep up with him.
That's true.
But I think it's important.
Thank you very much.
And you also have a very imaginative mind.
That kind of inspiration,
It comes out in your music, too,
but it also comes out in your cooking.
Oh!
Thank you very much.
That's for sure.
Please enjoy cooking.
Thank you very much.
Please come visit Hello Kitchen.
I will come.
Thank you very much.
That's all for Hello Kitchen.
Bye-bye.
Now, it's called meat pie. This time, you know, meat pies are delicious.
It's delicious, isn't it?
When I was in Seth's show, there was a café that served meat pies as part of the meal, and I love meat pies.
It's really delicious.
The first time I ate it, it was so delicious that my eyes widened.
I know what you mean.
It's so delicious that it's one of the things I look forward to when I go to Seth's. It's so delicious.
It's delicious. Even though it's cold, the meat is delicious.
Sometimes, there are times when the meat is freshly baked.
Oh, I see.
Sometimes they call out to you and say, "Oh, it's ready," and you say, "Oh, it's ready," and they say, "Oh, it's ready," and you say, "Oh, it's ready.
Like, "Oh, it's freshly baked.
Yes, that's right.
I'm trying to get it hot.
I see. So you're aiming for hot.
By all means.
Thank you very much. I got some good information here too.
And about cooking, Okada-chan, have you made anything recently?
Yes, I have. Since we are here today, in connection with bread, I made a pumpkin cream bun for Halloween.
Halloween is the time of pumpkin, isn't it?
That's right.
So we kneaded pumpkin into the dough and added regular custard cream.
Then we tie a string around the pumpkin to make it look like a pumpkin.
I don't know what to call it.
It was so cute, and of course it tasted delicious, so I thought I would like to make it again.
Do you give them to your members?
I served it to my family at that time, but I would like to bake some bread for the members someday.
I would like to bake something for the members someday. I'd be interested in that, too.
Yes, I would. Then it goes to me.
Yay!
Thank you very much.
Can I ask you more questions?
Yes, yes, yes.
Are you particular about the powder or the pumpkin or whatever?
Well, I'm not that particular yet, but I personally love bread.
That's right.
Yes, I do. I like breads like "Haruyokoi," which is a kind of spring roll, and so on.
I'm sorry, my reaction was a little weird.
Yes, yes.
So, maybe someday, when I get to a higher level, I can use flour, strong flour, or something like that.
I'd like to try to use strong flour.
That would be nice.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Oh, I'm sorry, this is completely personal.
Yes.
Also, there's some kind of northern aroma.
Ah, it's delicious.
Yes, it is.
Thank you very much.
Yes, it is. Thank you very much.
Hallo! STE.
Morning Musume。 24's Ayumi Ishida and Ajuna Matsumoto of Angulum will be presenting the "Halo! STE.
Morning Musume。24 will start their spring tour this weekend on March 16, and Angelem will start their spring tour on April 6.
Since we are just before their tour, I have selected some live videos of the other group's songs that give you the best sense of togetherness, and I will introduce them in order.
Yes, I chose Morning Musume。 I chose "Namidatch" as my favorite Morning Musume。
Let's take a look at the video of Morning Musume。 23 Concert Tour Autumn, Neverending Employee Award Sanctuary together.
Amazing!
Great picture!
This angle is really good!
Wow!
Wow, so cute!
Oh, it's so nice. This Namidacci chorus? The excitement and sense of unity is so great that it's truly one-of-a-kind.
And I have the image that every member of the band since the release of this song has some kind of attachment to this song.
Yeah!
We will all be shining stars someday!
Are we going to overflow!
It's kind of cool, isn't it?
Dairi is cute.
So cute!
But speaking of togetherness... the chorus after this...
Beautiful video. Amazing.
It's amazing!
I was watching from the audience, and I thought it was great.
I think it's really great.
I see. The lyrics aren't on the screen? No? No, right? Are they? Maybe not.
You know, it's amazing, the way you can really hear it.
I know, right?
You look good.
Beautiful.
The best part of Namidachi is the final chorus.
That's right.
I was watching from the audience that day.
I was watching from the audience that day, and I could feel the unity of the fans, and their voices were in unison.
And everyone on stage was so beautiful.
It was really great to see it from my point of view.
It's like another stage.
I think this song is only possible because of the fans.
I was so happy to be able to hear this song at Yokohama Arena.
Thank you very much.
At the end of this song, I think everyone had a good look on their faces.
At the very end of the song, after saying "Come on, Anne", they took a picture of me...
They always do that at every show.
Yes, yes, yes.
That picture is the real concert.
After the show was over, they showed it on the vision screen and said, "Thank you for today.
Like, "Thank you for today.
So, even though everyone is a bit rough around the edges, only at the moment of "Come on Anne" do they put on their best faces.
In fact, that was the only part where the audience was told not to make a fuss about anything.
I was told not to make a fuss about it.
That's right.
That's interesting.
That's why I thought they all looked so good.
Three seconds later, I asked them to pay attention and look at it one more time.
Okay. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Hallo! Sta.
My choice for the song with the best Angulum togetherness is
Human Life that we should love!
This time Angulum concert 2023
Big love Akari Takeuchi final live
Let's watch the video of From Angulum with Love together!
Cute.
Heisei's hair is long.
It's true.
Heisei is long too. So is Yuki Hirayama.
Yes, yes, yes.
Everyone is so cute.
I really, really like this kind of Angelem,
I can tell at a glance.
I can tell.
There were many strong songs in Angelem, but there are many more since they became Angelem,
The outfits of the members fit each other, and the songs have this feel to them.
It's cute.
Cute.
This is where it all starts, I think.
This is important!
Yay!
Yay! It's great! It's really great, isn't it?
I had the impression that the power of this song, the title "Big Love," and the presence of Akari Takeuchi, as well as the feelings that everyone has for her, were all expressed in this song.
I had the impression that this song really expresses the feelings of everyone towards her.
I was also impressed by the way Rikako hugged Takeuchi-san at the very side of the song.
That's the one that's all over the world, even in pictures, isn't it?
Our manager sent me a lot of pictures of this.
Everyone in the venue was like, "Wow! I'm sure they did it. I'm sure they did it.
We were all in the audience, and we were like, "Hey, look at that! So it was a great sense of unity that we all saw it like this.
That's for sure.
And now, when I look at the live video, including the camera work, we are a team including the staff.
So, I felt more togetherness.
Was that a surprise?
Yes, nothing at all. I don't know why we were moving around like that.
I see!
After the show, I received a lot of pictures of you, and I saw that you were holding Takeuchi-san in your arms.
That's right.
We had no idea.
You didn't see it?
We didn't see it!
Oh, no!
Heh heh heh heh.
That's right.
I see. I see.
I've been frantically moving around.
Oh, already.
Yes, sir.
So it was that kind of moment.
It was the kind of moment that neither Mr. Takeuchi nor Ms. Sasaki expected to be held in their arms.
That's interesting.
That was a miraculous moment of hugging, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
But I think it shows that such a coincidence really created a sense of togetherness.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Spring Storm. I like it. I like it.
Tofu laughed as he kicked God's balls.
I think we're about to get together.
You say you want to know about me, but...
But you say you want to know more about me
I'd rather do a gorilla run than any other girl.
I want to be more gorillanic than the other girls.
I can't ask you what it is that you like about me.
It's not like I'm a stranger.
You know what?
By the third set scene...
If we don't tie the knot, we're done.
I can't even look at you.
It's about confidence.
The third set scene...
You're going to confess, aren't you?
Dreams.
What should we do now that we're all together?
Haru-arashi I love you, I love you, but...
Lyrics, music, arrangement by Miku Hatsune
I'm looking into your eyes
On our third date
I hear you get used to it
In front of your chair
I'm trying to make it up to you
By the third date-see.
Even if the bubbles are on fire.
You know, if it comes down later...
There's a storm I like, but I like...
I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, but...
Thank you for watching.
Let's do our best again tomorrow.
This is Yumi Ishida from Morning Musume。 24 and
Yumi Ishida of Morning Musume 24 and Akena Matsumoto of Angstrom, will be presenting "Halo! STE.
It's time for us to say goodbye.
Here's an announcement!
Morning Musume。24 Concert Tour Spring
More Morning Musume。 will start on March 16th!
This is the first concert tour with 13 members.
The contents are very aggressive.
When I saw the set list
I had a feeling that it was going to be hard, so please look forward to it!
Please look forward to it!
Angulum Concert Tour 2024 Spring
Secret Secret Secret will start on April 6!
We will be touring various places around the country.
We will be touring in various places all over Japan, and with the upcoming graduation of Rikako Sasaki, we are going to perform the culmination of the current 11 members' performance.
I hope to show you the culmination of our current 11 members.
On March 30 and 31, we will be holding the Hina Fest at the Makuhari Messe International Exhibition
Hina Fest 2024 will be held at Makuhari Messe International Exhibition Hall 9 on March 30 and 31.
And on the same day, March 30 and 31, at the Makuhari Messe International Exhibition Hall
The "Carbon Neutral 2024 by Satosanzanoumi Movement" will also be held on March 30 and 31 at the Makuhari Messe International Exhibition Hall.
What kind of curry will be on sale this time?
Please come and visit us and see what kind of booths we will have!
Admission is free for those from Satosan-zan-kai.
Please come and visit us!
Morning Musume。24Angelum on May 3rd
BEYOND will perform at JAPAN JAM 2024 on May 4!
We are very excited to be able to perform at the festival again.
I don't know what it will be like yet, but I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm really looking forward to it and I'll do my best.
Hello STE is a channel where Hello Project members will be appearing more and more!
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday.
Please subscribe to our channel!
This time I'll be talking with Ayumi Ishida of Morning Musume 24 and Waka Matsumoto of Angeleum.
and Wakana Matsumoto of Angulum.
Good bye.
Farewell.
The end.
the end